<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tim Wu</title>
    <link>https://timvvvht.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tim Wu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2022; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://timvvvht.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>f(priors, inputs) -&gt; ideas</title>
      <link>https://timvvvht.github.io/blog/ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timvvvht.github.io/blog/ideas/</guid>
      <description>Novel Ideas If ideas are a function of priors and inputs, then it is paramount to (i) reduce reliance on priors; and/or (ii) increase quantity / quality of inputs.
If people are vessels through which ideas propagate, then it is essential to be connected to the &amp;ldquo;right&amp;rdquo; set of nodes.
Pre-EF Having spoken with a pretty representative sample of the upcoming LD19 cohort at Entrepreneur First, I am astonished by the sheer amount of talent, ambition, and drive emanating from these individuals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On the Demise of Ariadne</title>
      <link>https://timvvvht.github.io/blog/ariadne/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timvvvht.github.io/blog/ariadne/</guid>
      <description>In January 2022, I set out to solve a problem in the legal tech space.
From my stint as a lawyer, I noticed that a frustratingly high amount of time was spent on legal research. I conducted user interviews with numerous lawyers, who uniformly reverberated this sentiment - the existing legal research tools left much to be desired. One of them even told me &amp;ldquo;If a relevant case can&amp;rsquo;t be found by page x, then it doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On the Origins of my Sustained Infatuation with Computation</title>
      <link>https://timvvvht.github.io/blog/programming-odyssey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timvvvht.github.io/blog/programming-odyssey/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Surely there must be a better way of doing this&amp;rdquo;, I thought to myself, as I scoured the relevant directories for &amp;ldquo;proof&amp;rdquo; (in the form of a blurry jpeg) that X person was a graduate from Y university.
This was part-and-parcel of the process of legal due diligence, where every material statement necessitated &amp;ldquo;demonstrable evidence&amp;rdquo; - a Herculean yet seemingly Sisyphean task.
&amp;ldquo;If only there was a way to run a directory-wide &amp;lsquo;command-f&amp;rsquo; on images and scanned PDFs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I&#39;ve Built</title>
      <link>https://timvvvht.github.io/blog/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timvvvht.github.io/blog/projects/</guid>
      <description>Selected Projects (in reverse chronological order): A prototype of a DeFi interest rates swap platform, which enables users to manage their interest rates risk through trading the yield-bearing portion of their staked positions on the open market, powered by an on-chain central limit order book. Stack: Solidity, Javascript, React, Hardhat, Ethers.js Ariadne1 - a prototype of an AI-augmented legal search engine for legal judgments, with custom score function based on &amp;ldquo;weight-y&amp;rdquo; citations2 and nearest neighbours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About ☀️</title>
      <link>https://timvvvht.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timvvvht.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Live in the future, then build what&amp;rsquo;s missing. — Paul Graham
Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Tim, a self-starter and an absurdly quick learner with a fervent desire to facilitate epoch-defining impact through leveraging the potential of applied Artificial Intelligence and/or building infrastructure for the decentralised economy.
As an ex-cryptocurrency trader, lawyer, and a self-taught programmer, I have experience working across multiple domains and cognitive modalities, and am capable of rapidly shifting mental frameworks to the task(s) at hand.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
